Contact

m.a.touraji@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mehrdad-touraji-6a7bb3234 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Warehousing

Database Development

SQL

Languages

German (Limited Working)
Persian (Full Professional)
English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Data Warehouse
Data Science with Python
LookML in Looker
AWS Cloud Practitioner
Revenue Operations

Mehrdad Touraji

CS Ops| WFM | Data Vizz

Berlin, Berlin, Germany

Summary

Credentialed specialist and a self-starter supporting the development and optimization of processes, quality standards and KPIs, participating in enhancements initiatives for the operations team to enrich existing processes.

Best in using interpersonal skills to translate needs into requirements and conduct conceptual discussions with product owners, business architects, developers, and other stakeholders

I take ownership of customer issues reported for production and track them through resolution by benchmarking numbers, Batch, Python, SQL, metrics, strong communication skills, and experimentation.

Future education, media buying through a unified modification of traditional and online advertising, ML and NPL are some of my passions.

Experience

Trade Republic WFM - Intraday Management Specialist July 2022 - Present (6 months) Berlin, Germany

In this position, I find myself handling:

- Workforce management process/activity of daily attendance schedule adherence of Customer Service Associates in real-time, ensuring optimum service levels are achieved to deliver consistent performance.
- Analytics and turning insights into results by making data relevant, easy to consume and actionable.
- Utilising intuitive technology that eliminates mundane tasks and speeds resolutions of issues for better business outcomes.

Majorel
Quality Analyst
July 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 6 months)
Page 1 of 2

Serving quality assurance manager in marketing by delivering customer experience management (CXM) on behalf of some of the world's most respected brands. Analyzing key metrics (KPI) for a strong understanding of data lifecycle management and data governance and even stronger understanding of data management concepts and associated business processes and any BI tool that make data reliable and useful. Developing marketing performance & spend dashboards with key metrics for review with senior leadership and other cross-functional teams on site and global level.

Arvato CRM Solutions
Subject Matter Expert
August 2019 - July 2020 (1 year)
Berlin, Germany

Analyse market needs to derive product requirements. Support Product Managers and product teams in clustering and prioritization of requirements based on our customers' needs. Review product changes in the acceptance phase. Drive the analyze of operational aspects of our platform regarding legally compliance and perform the analysis and its automation of documents to ensure high quality. Anticipate to implications of product – market and customer trends, competitive responses, impact on partners, etc. and work closely with product development teams to ensure prioritization in line with our customer needs and assist in the go-to-market process. Constantly expanding knowledge with policy makers to keep up to date on changes and solve special cases independently and confidently using the tools at disposal and share expertise with colleagues from own and neighboring teams.

Education

Staffordshire University

Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (October 2013 - March 2017)

Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation (APU / APIIT)
Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering